Center for Environmental Management Records UA096
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Project Applications, Reviews, and Reports, 1986 -- 1996; UA096.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  - Projects, 1986 -- 1994; UA096.003.001
    - McCarthy, Kathryn, 1991; UA096.003.012.00036 (Box 12)
    - Miaoulis, Ioannis, 1991; UA096.003.012.00037 (Box 12)
    - Nickerson, Norton, 1991; UA096.003.012.00038 (Box 12)
    - Ofner, Peter, 1991; UA096.003.012.00039 (Box 12)
    - Pokras, Mark, 1991; UA096.003.012.00040 (Box 12)
    - Rappaport, Ann and Margaret Flaherty, 1991; UA096.003.012.00041 (Box 12)
    - Rappaport, et al., Talloires, 1991; UA096.003.012.00042 (Box 12)
    - Robbat, Albert, 1991; UA096.003.012.00043 (Box 12)
    - Schaffir, Rosalie, 1991; UA096.003.012.00044 (Box 12)
    - Soto, Ana, 1991; UA096.003.012.00045 (Box 12)
    - Stoukides, Michael, 1991; UA096.003.012.00046 (Box 12)
    - Stoukides, Michael and Albert Robbat, 1991; UA096.003.012.00047 (Box 12)
    - Talloires [ Amendment FFY'91, originial folder title listed wrong year], 1991; UA096.003.012.00048 (Box 12)
    - Talloires, 17K, 1991; UA096.003.012.00049 (Box 12)
    - Verma, Surendra, 1991; UA096.003.012.00050 (Box 12)
    - Walt, David R., 1991; UA096.003.012.00051 (Box 12)
    - Wetzler, Richard and Stephen Levine, 1991; UA096.003.012.00052 (Box 12)
    - Health division, 1991; UA096.003.012.00053 (Box 12)
    - Notice to PI's, 1991; UA096.003.012.00054 (Box 12)
    - Project Approval Forms, 1991; UA096.003.012.00055 (Box 12)
    - Current projects, 1992; UA096.003.012.00056 (Box 12)
    - Approvals and Budgets, 1992; UA096.003.012.00057 (Box 12)
    - Bostaris, 1992; UA096.003.012.00058 (Box 12)
    - Chabot, minority internships, 1992; UA096.003.012.00059 (Box 12)
    - Chabot, Teli, 1992; UA096.003.012.00060 (Box 12)
    - Chabot, Anne and Goldstein-Gelb, Warren, 1992; UA096.003.012.00061 (Box 12)
    - Chabot, Anne and Goldstein-Gelb, Warren, 1992; UA096.003.012.00062 (Box 12)
    - Chabot and Lipton, 1992; UA096.003.012.00063 (Box 12)
    - Chew, Mechaber, Webster, 1991; UA096.003.012.00064 (Box 12)
    - Collier and Manno, 1992; UA096.003.012.00065 (Box 12)
    - Creighton -- CLEAN!, 1992; UA096.003.012.00066 (Box 12)
    - Dillon and Baram, 1992; UA096.003.012.00067 (Box 12)
    - Ernst, 1992; UA096.003.012.00068 (Box 12)
    - Fischer and Chabot, 1992; UA096.003.012.00069 (Box 12)
    - Fischer (Peer Review), 1992; UA096.003.012.00070 (Box 12)
    - Fischer (QA), 1992; UA096.003.012.00071 (Box 12)
    - Flaherty and Rappaport, 1992; UA096.003.012.00072 (Box 12)
    - Goldner and Haas, 1992; UA096.003.012.00073 (Box 12)
    - Hecht, 1992; UA096.003.012.00074 (Box 12)
    - Ho, Shuk-Mei, 1992; UA096.003.012.00075 (Box 12)
    - Hyde/Gute, 1992; UA096.003.012.00076 (Box 12)
    - Illinger/Kenny, 1992; UA096.003.012.00077 (Box 12)
    - Kenny, 1992; UA096.003.012.00078 (Box 12)
    - Kline-Regional EPA 20K, 1992; UA096.003.012.00079 (Box 12)
    - Krimsky, 1992; UA096.003.012.00080 (Box 12)
    - Kounaves/Brush, 1992; UA096.003.012.00081 (Box 12)
    - Levy, 1992; UA096.003.012.00082 (Box 12)
    - Marlaret, Luis; Snyder (M. A. candidate), 1992; UA096.003.012.00083 (Box 12)
    - McCarthy, Kathryn; Considine (Ph.D. candidate), 1992; UA096.003.012.00084 (Box 12)
    - McCarthy/Sample, 1992; UA096.003.012.00085 (Box 12)
    - Miaoulis, 1992; UA096.003.012.00086 (Box 12)
    - Mitchell, 1992; UA096.003.012.00087 (Box 12)
    - Nickerson, 1992; UA096.003.012.00088 (Box 12)
    - Noble, 1992; UA096.003.012.00089 (Box 12)
    - Reinisch, 1992; UA096.003.012.00090 (Box 12)
    - Robbat, 1992; UA096.003.012.00091 (Box 12)
    - Stoukides/Robbat, 1992; UA096.003.012.00092 (Box 12)
    - Teichman, 1992; UA096.003.012.00093 (Box 12)
    - Verma, 1992; UA096.003.012.00094 (Box 12)
    - Wetzler/Levine, 1992; UA096.003.012.00095 (Box 12)
    - Project applications., 1992; UA096.003.012.00096 (Box 12)
    - Final project reports guidelines, 1993; UA096.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
      The year is fiscal year.
    - Review Panel, 1993; UA096.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
    - Review Process Memo, 1993; UA096.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
    - Current Projects, 1993; UA096.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
    - Albertini, 1993; UA096.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
    - Anderson, 1993; UA096.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
    - Botsaris, 1993; UA096.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
    - Chabot, 1993; UA096.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
    - Chew, 1993; UA096.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
    - Collier, 1993; UA096.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
    - Creighton, 1993; UA096.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
    - Dillon/Baram, 1993; UA096.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
    - Ernst, 1993; UA096.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
    - Fischer, 1993; UA096.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
    - Fischer, 1993; UA096.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
    - Fischer, 1993; UA096.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
    - Goldner/Haas, 1993; UA096.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
    - Goldstein-Gelb Ochinang, 1993; UA096.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
    - Gotelli/Rappaport. Grad Student, 1993; UA096.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
    - Gute/Hyde, 1993; UA096.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
    - Hollister, 1993; UA096.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
    - Illinger/Kenny, 1993; UA096.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
    - Kelly, 1993; UA096.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
    - Kenny, 1993; UA096.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
    - Kieffer (student), 1993; UA096.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
    - Kline, 1993; UA096.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
    - Kounves, 1993; UA096.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
    - Krimsky, 1993; UA096.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
    - Levy, 1993; UA096.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
    - Levine/Wetzler, 1993; UA096.003.013.00030 (Box 13)
    - Lockeretz/Anderson, 1993; UA096.003.013.00031 (Box 13)
    - Lockeretz, 1993; UA096.003.013.00032 (Box 13)
    - Miaoulis, 1993; UA096.003.013.00033 (Box 13)
    - McCarthy, 1993; UA096.003.013.00034 (Box 13)
    - Mitchell, 1993; UA096.003.013.00035 (Box 13)
    - Moomaw, 1993; UA096.003.013.00036 (Box 13)
    - Nickerson, 1993; UA096.003.013.00037 (Box 13)
    - Noble, 1993; UA096.003.013.00038 (Box 13)
    - Ofner, 1993; UA096.003.013.00039 (Box 13)
    - Pokras, 1993; UA096.003.013.00040 (Box 13)
    - Reinisch, 1993; UA096.003.013.00041 (Box 13)
    - Robbat, 1993; UA096.003.013.00042 (Box 13)
    - Schultz, 1993; UA096.003.013.00043 (Box 13)
    - Stoukides/Eng, 1993; UA096.003.013.00044 (Box 13)
    - Verma, 1993; UA096.003.013.00045 (Box 13)
    - Vogel/Fennessey, 1993; UA096.003.013.00046 (Box 13)
    - Walt, 1993; UA096.003.013.00047 (Box 13)
    - Weaver, 1993; UA096.003.013.00048 (Box 13)
    - Windmiller/Chew, 1993; UA096.003.013.00049 (Box 13)
    - Copies of Approved Cover Sheets, 1993; UA096.003.013.00050 (Box 13)
    - Final report tracking, 1993; UA096.003.013.00051 (Box 13)
    - Guide to RFA FY93 Disks, 1993; UA096.003.013.00052 (Box 13)
    - Abraham, 1994; UA096.003.013.00053 (Box 13)
    - Albertini, 1994; UA096.003.013.00054 (Box 13)
    - Alcivar-Warren, 1994; UA096.003.013.00055 (Box 13)
    - Botsaris, 1994; UA096.003.013.00056 (Box 13)
    - Chabot, 1994; UA096.003.013.00057 (Box 13)
    - Chew, 1994; UA096.003.013.00058 (Box 13)
    - Cless, 1994; UA096.003.013.00059 (Box 13)
    - Collier, 1994; UA096.003.013.00060 (Box 13)
    - Creighton, 1994; UA096.003.013.00061 (Box 13)
    - Derbernardez-Clark, 1994; UA096.003.013.00062 (Box 13)
    - Dillon, 1994; UA096.003.013.00063 (Box 13)
    - Fischer, 1994; UA096.003.013.00064 (Box 13)
    - Flessas (Student), 1994; UA096.003.013.00065 (Box 13)
    - Goldner, 1994; UA096.003.013.00066 (Box 13)
    - Kelly, 1994; UA096.003.013.00067 (Box 13)
    - Kenny, 1994; UA096.003.013.00068 (Box 13)
    - Kline, 1994; UA096.003.013.00069 (Box 13)
    - Kounaves, 1994; UA096.003.013.00070 (Box 13)
    - Krimsky, 1994; UA096.003.013.00071 (Box 13)
    - Levy, 1994; UA096.003.013.00072 (Box 13)
    - Levy, 1994; UA096.003.013.00073 (Box 13)
    - Lockeretz, 1994; UA096.003.013.00074 (Box 13)
    - Matthews ( student), 1994; UA096.003.013.00075 (Box 13)
    - Miaolis, 1994; UA096.003.013.00076 (Box 13)
    - Moomaw, 1994; UA096.003.013.00077 (Box 13)
    - Noble, 1994; UA096.003.013.00078 (Box 13)
    - Ofner, 1994; UA096.003.013.00079 (Box 13)
    - Pokras, 1994; UA096.003.013.00080 (Box 13)
    - Pokras (Loons), 1994; UA096.003.013.00081 (Box 13)
    - Portney, 1994; UA096.003.013.00082 (Box 13)
    - Rappaport, 1994; UA096.003.013.00083 (Box 13)
    - Robbat, 1994; UA096.003.013.00084 (Box 13)
    - Rotberg (student), 1994; UA096.003.013.00085 (Box 13)
    - Schultz, 1994; UA096.003.013.00086 (Box 13)
    - Soto, 1994; UA096.003.013.00087 (Box 13)
    - Tai (student), 1994; UA096.003.013.00088 (Box 13)
    - Verma, 1994; UA096.003.013.00089 (Box 13)
    - Vogel, 1994; UA096.003.013.00090 (Box 13)
    - Walt, 1994; UA096.003.013.00091 (Box 13)
    - Weaver, 1994; UA096.003.013.00092 (Box 13)
    - Wetzler, 1994; UA096.003.013.00093 (Box 13)
    - Wetzler (Env. studies), 1994; UA096.003.013.00094 (Box 13)
    - FY 1994 Award Handbook, UA096.003.013.00095 (Box 13)
    - FY94 Current Projects Publication, 1994; UA096.003.013.00096 (Box 13)
    - Dissemination of Results, 1994; UA096.003.013.00097 (Box 13)
    - Faxes to potential reviewers, 1994; UA096.003.013.00098 (Box 13)
    - Feedback, 1994; UA096.003.013.00099 (Box 13)
    - Funding Process Summary, 1994; UA096.003.013.00100 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Student Flyer, 1994; UA096.003.013.00101 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994; UA096.003.013.00102 (Box 13)
    - Program announcements and request for application, 1994; UA096.003.014.00001 (Box 14)
    - Preproprosals Interdisciplinary Projects, 1994; UA096.003.014.00002 (Box 14)
    - Release, 1994; UA096.003.014.00003 (Box 14)
    - Review Process Memo, 1994; UA096.003.014.00004 (Box 14)
    - RFA, 1994; UA096.003.014.00005 (Box 14)
    - RFA background (Old CEM RFAs, etc.), 1994; UA096.003.014.00006 (Box 14)
    - RFA disk information, 1994; UA096.003.014.00007 (Box 14)
    - Signed Coversheets, 1994; UA096.003.014.00008 (Box 14)
    - Summary of Allocations of U.S. EPA funds, 1994; UA096.003.014.00009 (Box 14)
    - U.S. EPA Project Advisor Reviews, 1994; UA096.003.014.00010 (Box 14)
    - Ellmore, 1994; UA096.003.014.00011 (Box 14)
    - Ernst, 1994; UA096.003.014.00012 (Box 14)
    - Flaherty/von Lazar, 1994; UA096.003.014.00013 (Box 14)
    - Goldstein-Gelb/Abruzzi, 1994; UA096.003.014.00014 (Box 14)
    - Gute, 1994; UA096.003.014.00015 (Box 14)
    - Illinger/Kenny/Moomaw, 1994; UA096.003.014.00016 (Box 14)
    - Jacobson, 1994; UA096.003.014.00017 (Box 14)
    - Kline-revised, 1994; UA096.003.014.00018 (Box 14)
    - Final reports discs assistance agreement, #CR813481, 1994; UA096.003.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Project Reports, 1986 -- 1996; UA096.003.002
    - Abedian, B., et al., Electroosmosis for toxic waste control at hazardous waste sites a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1989; UA096.003.014.00020 (Box 14)
    - Armoudlian, A.S., et al., Capacity of created wetlands for treatment of landfill leachate, 1991; UA096.003.014.00021 (Box 14)
    - Baram, M.S., et al., Managing chemical risks: corporate response to SARA title III, 1990; UA096.003.014.00022 (Box 14)
    - Botsaris, G.D., Crystallization of calcium magnesium acetate for environmental applications, 1996; UA096.003.014.00023 (Box 14)
    - Bramante, C.M., et al., Pollution prevention in an academic setting: a case study at Tufts University, 1990; UA096.003.014.00024 (Box 14)
    - Chudyk, W., Fiber-optic laser-induced fluorescence in field monitoring of ground water contaminants, 1990; UA096.003.014.00025 (Box 14)
    - Chudyk, W., Laser fluorescence/fiber optic monitoring of groundwater contaminant biodegration final technical report, 1987; UA096.003.014.00026 (Box 14)
    - Collier, R.D., et al., Thermal acoustic tomography simulation and reconstruction algorithms for temperature fields in combustion furnaces, 1995; UA096.003.014.00027 (Box 14)
    - Creighton, S.H., et al., Solid waste reduction in colleges and universities: a status report, 1993; UA096.003.014.00028 (Box 14)
    - Dillon, P.S., et al., Environmental management in corporations: methods and motivations, 1992; UA096.003.014.00029 (Box 14)
    - Dillon, P.S., ed., Local management of chemical risks, 1990; UA096.003.014.00030 (Box 14)
    - Dillon, P.S., et al., Survey of environmental management practices of small businesses, 1993; UA096.003.014.00031 (Box 14)
    - Edgers, L., et al., A model for long term settlement in landfills, 1990; UA096.003.014.00032 (Box 14)
    - Edgers, L., et al., Field station feasibility study final report, 1988; UA096.003.014.00033 (Box 14)
    - Ernst, S.G., Electromagnetic fields on animal development, 1994; UA096.003.014.00034 (Box 14)
    - Flaherty, M.F., et al., An environmental brief privatization and environment in Hungary a case study, 1992 -- 1993; UA096.003.014.00035 (Box 14)
      This date is an approximate.
    - Flaherty, M., et al., Multinational corporations and the environment: a survey of global practices, 1991; UA096.003.014.00036 (Box 14)
      Includes 3.5-inch diskette.
    - Gankin, Y.V., et al., Identification of PCB congeners by gas chromatography electron capture detection employing a quantitative structure-retention model, 1995; UA096.003.014.00037 (Box 14)
    - Geiger, K., et al., Foreign practices in hazardous waste minimization a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1986; UA096.003.014.00038 (Box 14)
    - Golding, D., et al., Radon risk communication in context: an experiment in Massachusetts a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1990; UA096.003.014.00039 (Box 14)
    - Golding, D., et al., Radon risk communication in context: an experiment in Massachusetts a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1990; UA096.003.014.00040 (Box 14)
    - Green, S.N., et al., Planning for hazardous waste capacity: lessons from the Northeast states executive summary, 1990; UA096.003.014.00041 (Box 14)
    - Green, S.N., et al., Planning for hazardous waste capacity: lessons from the Northeast states, 1990; UA096.003.014.00042 (Box 14)
    - Hecht, N.B., Biological markers to detect DNA damage in the testis following exposure to toxicants, 1991; UA096.003.014.00043 (Box 14)
    - Ho, S., et al., Adverse health effects of environmental estrogens and cadmium on the prostate, 1992; UA096.003.014.00044 (Box 14)
    - Jacobson, S., final report, 1990 -- 1995; UA096.003.014.00045 (Box 14)
      This date is approximate. Includes 3.5-inch diskette.
    - Kenny, J., Monitoring of aqueous pollutants using laser-excited fluorescence array spectroscopy, 1993; UA096.003.014.00046 (Box 14)
    - Kline, E., et al., Promising techniques: hazardous waste siting process, 1993; UA096.003.014.00047 (Box 14)
    - Konishi, A., Comparison of policy and accounting systems for municipal solid waste management in Japan and the United States, 1991; UA096.003.015.00001 (Box 15)
    - Kounaves, S.P., Microelectrode for heavy metal analysis, 1992; UA096.003.015.00002 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Agricultural biotechnology: an environmental outlook, 1993; UA096.003.015.00003 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Emerging paradigms of risk and risk communication, 1991; UA096.003.015.00004 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Environmental hazards: communicating risks as a social process, 1988; UA096.003.015.00005 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication case study no. 1 the release of genetically modified organisms in the environment: the case of ice minus, 1988; UA096.003.015.00006 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication case study no. 2 a natural environmental hazard: the case of radon, 1988; UA096.003.015.00007 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication case study no. 3 pesticide residues in food: the case of EDB, 1988; UA096.003.015.00008 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication case study no. 4 an industrial plant: the case of the ASARCO/Tacoma copper smelter, 1988; UA096.003.015.00009 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication case study no. 5 a hazardous waste site: the case of Nyanza, 1988; UA096.003.015.00010 (Box 15)
    - Krimsky, S., et al., Project on improving risk communication executive summary, 1988; UA096.003.015.00011 (Box 15)
    - Leav, I., The detection of oncogene expression for assessing carcinogenic potential of environmental chemicals, 1991; UA096.003.015.00012 (Box 15)
    - Levy, B.S., Facilitating a systematic multisectoral approach to environmental health policy and program development: application to lead poisoning prevention in Hungary, part 1 of 3 [packet], 1994; UA096.003.015.00013 (Box 15)
    - Levy, B.S., Facilitating a systematic multisectoral approach to environmental health policy and program development: application to lead poisoning prevention in Hungary, part 2 of 3 [packet], 1994; UA096.003.015.00014 (Box 15)
    - Levy, B.S., Facilitating a systematic multisectoral approach to environmental health policy and program development: application to lead poisoning prevention in Hungary, part 3 of 3 [packet], 1994; UA096.003.015.00015 (Box 15)
    - Levy, B., et al., From science to action: the lead hazard in Hungary-a fact report, 1996; UA096.003.015.00016 (Box 15)
    - Matula, R., The identification and thermal stability of intermediate compounds produced during the incineration of chlorinated hydrocarbons, 1986; UA096.003.015.00017 (Box 15)
    - McCarthy, K.A., Acousto-optic spectrometry for pollution detection, 1993; UA096.003.015.00018 (Box 15)
    - Mechaber, W.L., et al., Biological mechanisms for bio-rational control of cranberry weevil, Anthonomus musculus, 1995; UA096.003.015.00019 (Box 15)
    - Mechaber, W.L., Ecology of Anthonomus musculus; hostplant finding and exploitation by cranberry weevil, part 1 of 2 [packet], 1992; UA096.003.015.00020 (Box 15)
    - Mechaber, W.L., Ecology of Anthonomus musculus: hostplant finding and exploitation by cranberry weevil, part 2 of 2 [packet], 1992; UA096.003.015.00021 (Box 15)
    - Meldon, J., Characterization of novel nitric oxide scrubbing media a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1990; UA096.003.015.00022 (Box 15)
    - Meldon, J.H., Curriculum material in chemical engineering featuring waste minimization concepts, 1990; UA096.003.015.00023 (Box 15)
    - Miaoulis, I.N., Development of a novel diesel engine cold start aid system using exhaust waste heat, 1992; UA096.003.015.00024 (Box 15)
    - Mitchell, G.H., Jr., Trade and environment: the U.S. role, draft and comments, 1994; UA096.003.015.00025 (Box 15)
    - Nickerson, N.H., study of the edaphic factors controlling die-off and heights of mangrove species on outlying reef islands in Belize, 1993; UA096.003.015.00026 (Box 15)
    - Noble, J.J., Executive summary systems model for sanitary landfill dynamics phase II: moisture flow analysis phase III: pilot experimentation, 1993; UA096.003.015.00027 (Box 15)
    - Noble, J.J., et al., Experimental and mathematical modeling of moisture transport in landfills, 1990; UA096.003.015.00028 (Box 15)
      Includes 8-inch diskette.
    - Noble, J.J., Final report systems fundamentals for product/process lifestyle audit, 1993; UA096.003.015.00029 (Box 15)
    - Ofner, P., et al., An animal model for detection of early pre-neoplastic effects of hormonal and non-hormonla agents of the prostate, 1991; UA096.003.015.00030 (Box 15)
    - Ofner, P., et al., Markers of oxidative stress caused by exposure to environmental toxins, 1995; UA096.003.015.00031 (Box 15)
    - Pilgrim, H.G., Global classroom project: the environment, international politics, and the superpowers a report to the United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1989; UA096.003.015.00032 (Box 15)
    - Pokras, M.A., Environmental pathology of 124 common loons from the Northeastern United States, 1989-1992, 1993; UA096.003.015.00033 (Box 15)
    - Portney, K.E., After facilities are sitied: an evaluation of satisfaction with sited facilities, siting agreements, and their implementation, 1995; UA096.003.015.00034 (Box 15)
    - Rappaport, A., et al., Global corporate environment, health, and safety programs: management principles and practices, 1991; UA096.003.015.00035 (Box 15)
    - Reiter, A.J., Hazardous waste generation in the United States and Japan: a comparative analysis, 1991; UA096.003.015.00036 (Box 15)
    - Rest, K., et al., Risk communication and community right-to-know: a four community study of SARA title III, 1991; UA096.003.015.00037 (Box 15)
    - Robbat, A., Jr., Thermal desorption gas chromatography/mass spectrometry (TDGC/MS) on-site detection of EPA targeted organic compounds at superfund sites, 1993; UA096.003.015.00038 (Box 15)
    - Rotberg, F.J.Y., A comparative analysis of two community forestry initiatives in Costa Rica: a mechanism for sustainable development?, 1994; UA096.003.015.00039 (Box 15)
    - Rowan, A.N., Alternatives to animal testing project report 10/88 to 6/92, 1993; UA096.003.015.00040 (Box 15)
    - Saugus River water quality monitoring program, background and resources handbook, 1992; UA096.003.016.00001 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Shanabruch, W., Development of a eukaryotic chromotest for the rapid detection of genotoxic, 1993; UA096.003.016.00002 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., An action plan for the protection of the Saugus River, 1991; UA096.003.016.00003 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., Developing corporate/public environmental partnerships: a case study of river protection in Massachusetts, outline, 1992; UA096.003.016.00004 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., Developing corporate/public environmental partnerships: a case study of river protection in Massachusetts, rough draft, 1993; UA096.003.016.00005 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., Developing corporate/public environmental partnerships: a case study of r iver protection in Massachusetts, rough draft, 1993; UA096.003.016.00006 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., Developing corporate/public environmental partnerships: a case study of river protection in Massachusetts, 1993; UA096.003.016.00007 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
      This date is approximate.
    - Snyder, R., The Saugus River: a resource at risk, 1993; UA096.003.016.00008 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Snyder, R., The Saugus River: a resource at risk, 1993; UA096.003.016.00009 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Stoukides, M., et al., Fundamental studied of incineration of contaminated soils using the electrodynamic thermogravimetric analyzer, 1992; UA096.003.016.00010 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Stoukides, M., Solid electrolyte aided decomposition of hydrogen sulfide, 1992; UA096.003.016.00011 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Tai, S., Global warming potentials and infrared intensities of technological gases: experimental and computation studies, 1995; UA096.003.016.00012 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Verma, S.P., Effects of pesticides on membrane structure: laser raman study, 1991; UA096.003.016.00013 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Verma, S.P., Electromagnetic field-induced changes in the structure/activity of protein kinases, 1993; UA096.003.016.00014 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Verma, S.P., On mechanism(s) of herbicide-induced proliferative lung cell changes, 1993; UA096.003.016.00015 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Walt, D.R., Continuous monitoring of groundwater using fiber optic chemical sensors, 1993; UA096.003.016.00016 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Walt, D.R., Preparation of fiber optic immunosensors for atrazine, 1995; UA096.003.016.00017 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
    - Wetzler, R.E., Ecological risk baselines for transgenic releases: the survival and spreading of wild-type and mutant Pseudomonas fluorescens populations in native soil, 1993; UA096.003.016.00018 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
- Publications, 1985 -- 1994; UA096.004; 1.2 Linear Feet